<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="147311" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="Civic Voice" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Bring democracy to your city! Citizens propose projects, vote on initiatives and elect a mayor whose agenda shapes the city." />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<LongDescription>
		Civic Voice adds a living governance layer to your city. Citizens submit proposals based on your city's real needs, vote in annual mayoral elections and hold you accountable for the state of your city.

		**Citizen Proposals**
		Citizens submit proposals based on your city's real needs. High unemployment? Residents demand job creation. Housing shortage? Citizens call for new development. Proposals are driven by live city data so they always feel relevant to your current situation.

		**Three Tiers of Projects**
		- Urgent Issues — triggered automatically when city metrics fall below acceptable levels
		- Citizen Proposals — general improvements influenced by the current mayor's specialty
		- Major Projects — ambitious year-long undertakings like a new port, university campus or signature landmark

		**Mayoral Elections**
		Every year your city holds a democratic election. Two candidates campaign with distinct specialties and slogans. Endorse your preferred candidate to add your influence — but the citizens decide. The winning mayor's specialty influences which proposals citizens bring forward.

		**Note**
		Civic Voice is a roleplay and immersion mod. It reads your city's real data to generate meaningful proposals and elections but does not directly modify gameplay mechanics.

		Safe to add or remove from any city at any time. Does not conflict with other mods.
	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="0.1.0" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.2.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<!--Required DLC, can be set multiple times-->
	<RequiredDLC Value="" />
	<!--Change log for new version-->
	<ChangeLog Value="0.1.0 - Initial beta release" />
	<!--External link-->
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/xTrueF/CivicVoice" />
	<!--Supported values Public, Private, Unlisted-->
	<AccessLevel Value="Public" />
</Publish>